<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>novem on Maiche Jewan</title>
    <link>/categories/novem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in novem on Maiche Jewan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/novem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tendli (Ivy gourd) mix</title>
      <link>/post/tendli-ivy-gourd-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tendli-ivy-gourd-mix/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg tendli (ivy gourd), sliced in 6 julienne style pieces 2 onions, medium-sized, sliced 1 tomato, large, sliced 4 green chilies, slit in half 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger, minced 8-9 garlic cloves, crushed 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp turmeric powder 1 tsp black mustard seeds 10-15 curry leaves 1&amp;frasl;2 cup, fresh coconut, grated 3 tbsp, cooking oil salt, as per taste  Method: Take a pan and add oil. When the oil is warm, add mustard seeds, crushed garlic and curry leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gosalen (Ridge gourd)</title>
      <link>/post/gosalen-ridge-gourd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gosalen-ridge-gourd/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg, gosalen or ridge gourd, sliced &amp;amp; diced in 4 quarters 2 onions, medium-sized, diced fine 2 tomatoes, medium-sized, diced fine 5 green chillies, slit in half 8-9 garlic cloves, crished 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger, minced 1 tsp urad dal (white lentils) 1 tsp black mustard seeds 10 curry leaves 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 1&amp;frasl;4 cup, fresh coconut, grated 4 red chilli peppers, small and round, dried 3 tbsp cooking oil salt, as per taste  Method: Take a pan and add oil, and when warm add the urad dal, mustard seeds, red small round chilies, garlic crushed, curry leaves, green chilies and ginger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French beans tel piyao</title>
      <link>/post/french-beans-tel-piyao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/french-beans-tel-piyao/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;French beans tel piyao&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprouted mung (green lentils)</title>
      <link>/post/sprouted-moong-green-lentils/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sprouted-moong-green-lentils/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;4 kg, mung (green whole lentils), soaked overnight 2 onions,medium-sized, sliced 2 tomatoes, medium-sized, sliced 3 green chilies, slit in half 1&amp;rdquo; ginger, chopped fine 6-7 garlic cloves, crushed 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp shahjeera (caraway seeds) 1 tsp, mustard seeds 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 1 tsp red chilly powder 1 tsp garam masala 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves, minced 10 curry leaves 4 tbsp, oil salt, as per taste 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water  Method: Soak the mung dal overnight and drain the water out the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>