<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fish on Maiche Jewan</title>
    <link>/categories/fish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fish on Maiche Jewan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/fish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Steamed Fish</title>
      <link>/post/steamed_fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/steamed_fish/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients To marinate the fish - 1 kg, fish fillets, or whole fish (fish of your choice; preference pomfret) - 1”, ginger, crushed - 12 cloves, garlic crushed/finely sliced - 2 tsp, red chilly powder - 1 tsp, cumin powder - 1 tsp, garam masala - ½ tsp, turmeric powder - 2-3 tbsp, lemon juice - salt, as per taste
For the mix - 2 large, tomatoes, chopped in big cubes - 2 large, onions, chopped in big cubes - ½ tsp, ginger, finely chopped - 3-4 cloves, garlice, finely sliced - 2-3, green chillies, slit along the length in half - 1 cup, bell peppers / capsicum (red, orange, yellow), sliced fine - ½ tsp, black pepper powder - 2, bay leaves - 3 tbsp, coriander leaves, finely chopped - 2 tbsp, oil - Optional (may add broccoli, carrots, zucchini/courgetti, or any veggie of your choice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish cutlets</title>
      <link>/post/fish-cutlets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fish-cutlets/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  500 g fish of your choice (mackerel/tuna/kingfish) 1 potato, boiled and mashed 2 medium-sized onlion, chopped fine 3 green chillies ,chopped fine 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves, chopped fine 5-6 mint leaves, chopped fine 1 tbsp., ginger and garlic paste 1 tsp, turmeric powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. red chilly powder 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp, garam masala powder 2 tsp vinegar / Lemon juice salt, as per taste 2 cups, bread crumbs 2 cups, water 1 egg, beaten cooking oil (for frying)  Method: Clean the fish, cut into big pieces and put in a pan with 2 cups of water, 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ambot teek (fish curry)</title>
      <link>/post/ambot-teek-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ambot-teek-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ambot teek (fish curry)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginger Garlic Fish</title>
      <link>/post/ginger-garlic-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ginger-garlic-fish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yet another quick dish&amp;hellip;these are especially for those times when
guests come in uninvited or you’ve had enough of the chicken or meat.
Boneless fish is the best pick for this one&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maiche maasli kodi (Mum&#39;s fish Curry)</title>
      <link>/post/masali-kodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/masali-kodi/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: (Serves 4-5 persons)  1 kg fish of your choice  For the paste:  2 onions, medium-size 2 tsps red chilly Powder 2 tsp coriander powder 1 tsp cumin powder 1 green chilly 7 garlic cloves 1 tomato - large / 1 tbsp curd 7 Vonti Solan (dried Monkey Jack seeds) / Tamarind (size of a lemon) 7-8 curry leaves 1&amp;frasl;2 freshly grated coconut / 1 can coconut milk Salt to taste  For the pan:  1 onion - small-sized; finely sliced 2 green chillies - slit in half 1&amp;frasl;2 inch ginger - finely chopped 2 tbsp oil 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves - finely chopped to garnish  Method: Grind all above ingredients to a fine paste.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>