<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Maiche Jewan</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Maiche Jewan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kulkuls (Kedios)</title>
      <link>/post/kulkul/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kulkul/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kulkuls(Kedios)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ragi Mandas</title>
      <link>/post/ragi_mandas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ragi_mandas/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 cups, ragi (finger millet flour) 1 cup, rice flour 2 tbsp cooked rice 2½ cup, jaggery, grated ½ tsp, cardamom powder a pinch of nutmeg powder 1 tsp, butter salt, as per taste  Method:
Grind all the above ingredients (except cardamom and nutmeg powder) with water and make a thick batter like dosa/pancake batter. Add the cardamom and nutmeg powder, mix and check the sweetness, to see if you’d like to add more jaggery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steamed Fish</title>
      <link>/post/steamed_fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/steamed_fish/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients To marinate the fish - 1 kg, fish fillets, or whole fish (fish of your choice; preference pomfret) - 1”, ginger, crushed - 12 cloves, garlic crushed/finely sliced - 2 tsp, red chilly powder - 1 tsp, cumin powder - 1 tsp, garam masala - ½ tsp, turmeric powder - 2-3 tbsp, lemon juice - salt, as per taste
For the mix - 2 large, tomatoes, chopped in big cubes - 2 large, onions, chopped in big cubes - ½ tsp, ginger, finely chopped - 3-4 cloves, garlice, finely sliced - 2-3, green chillies, slit along the length in half - 1 cup, bell peppers / capsicum (red, orange, yellow), sliced fine - ½ tsp, black pepper powder - 2, bay leaves - 3 tbsp, coriander leaves, finely chopped - 2 tbsp, oil - Optional (may add broccoli, carrots, zucchini/courgetti, or any veggie of your choice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shankerpali (thukdio)</title>
      <link>/post/shankarpali/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shankarpali/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 cups, maida (all-purpose flour) ¼ cup, rava (semolina, fine) 1 cup, castor sugar 1 pinch, baking soda ½ tsp, vanilla essence 2 cups, water, to make sugar syrup salt, as per taste 2tbsp, ghee 500g, ghee, for frying  Method Take a pan and add 2 cups of water and 1 cup sugar and boil to make a thin syrup and keep aside to cool.
Take a big bowl and put the maida, rava, baking soda, salt, 2 tbsp of warm ghee, vanilla essence and mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pahadi Chicken Masala</title>
      <link>/post/pahadi_chicken_masala/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pahadi_chicken_masala/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 kg, chicken, medium-sized pieces 1 large, onion, chopped 2”, ginger, finely chopped 1 pod (7-8 cloves), garlic, finely chopped 7-8, green chillies, finely chopped 10-12 leaves, mint, finely chopped 1½ tbsp, lime juice (or a lemon-size ball of tamarind) ½ tsp turmeric powder 2 tsp, ginger paste 2 tsp, garlic paste whole spices (5 cloves, 7 black pepper corns, 2 cinnamon sticks, 2 cardamom, 2 bay leaves) 2 bunches, coriander leaves, finely chopped salt, as per taste oil for frying  Method For the paste, grind together the following ingredients: onion, green chillies, ginger, garlic, mint leaves, coriander leaves, full spices and tamarind or lemon Juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken with eggplant</title>
      <link>/post/chicken-with-eggplant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chicken-with-eggplant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chicken with eggplant&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Chops</title>
      <link>/post/porkchops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/porkchops/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 Kg, pork Chops 1 tsp, ginger paste 1 tsp, garlic paste 1 tsp, turmeric powder 1 tsp, bafat powder whole spices ( 5 cloves, 7-8 black pepper corns, 2 cinnamon sticks, 1 cardamom, 2 bay leaves) sauces (1tbsp BBQ sauce, 2 tbsp chilly garlic sauce, 1 tbsp Worcestershire sauce, 1 tbsp vinegar, 1 tsp lemon juice or 1 tbsp yoghurt, 2 tbsp honey, 1tbsp olive oil) salt, as per taste 2 tbsp, oil  Method Mix all the ingredients for the sauce and keep aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minced Green Peas</title>
      <link>/post/mince_greenpeas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mince_greenpeas/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 kg, mutton mince 2 large, onions, chopped 2 large, tomatoes, chopped 1” ginger, finely chopped 10 cloves, garlic, finely chopped 1 cup, green peas, boiled 1 tsp, ginger paste 1 tsp, garlic paste 3 tbsp, yoghurt 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp, turmeric powder 1tsp, red chilly powder 2tsp, coriander powder 1tsp, cumin powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp, black pepper powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp, garam masala 3-4, green chillies, finely chopped 1&amp;frasl;2 cup, coriander leaves, finely chopped whole spices (2 cloves, 2 cinnamon sticks, 2 cardamom, 2 bay leaves) 3-4tbsp, oil or ghee salt, as per taste  Method Wash and drain the water from the mince in the strainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karam (Cucumber salad)</title>
      <link>/post/karam-cucumber-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/karam-cucumber-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  3 cucumbers 1 onion, small, chopped fine 1&amp;frasl;2 cup fresh coconut, grated fine 3 green chillies, cut fine 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger, minced 4 garlic cloves, minced 1 tsp black mustard seeds 1 tbsp vinegar or lemon juice salt, as per taste  Method: Peel the cucumbers and mince them. Add salt and vinegar/lemon juice and keep aside for an hour. After an hour, squeeze out the excess water from the minced cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tendli (Ivy gourd) mix</title>
      <link>/post/tendli-ivy-gourd-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tendli-ivy-gourd-mix/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg tendli (ivy gourd), sliced in 6 julienne style pieces 2 onions, medium-sized, sliced 1 tomato, large, sliced 4 green chilies, slit in half 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger, minced 8-9 garlic cloves, crushed 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp turmeric powder 1 tsp black mustard seeds 10-15 curry leaves 1&amp;frasl;2 cup, fresh coconut, grated 3 tbsp, cooking oil salt, as per taste  Method: Take a pan and add oil. When the oil is warm, add mustard seeds, crushed garlic and curry leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>alasande-cow-pea</title>
      <link>/post/alasande-cow-pea-or-black-eyed-pea-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/alasande-cow-pea-or-black-eyed-pea-beans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;alasande-cow-pea&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gosalen (Ridge gourd)</title>
      <link>/post/gosalen-ridge-gourd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gosalen-ridge-gourd/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg, gosalen or ridge gourd, sliced &amp;amp; diced in 4 quarters 2 onions, medium-sized, diced fine 2 tomatoes, medium-sized, diced fine 5 green chillies, slit in half 8-9 garlic cloves, crished 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger, minced 1 tsp urad dal (white lentils) 1 tsp black mustard seeds 10 curry leaves 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 1&amp;frasl;4 cup, fresh coconut, grated 4 red chilli peppers, small and round, dried 3 tbsp cooking oil salt, as per taste  Method: Take a pan and add oil, and when warm add the urad dal, mustard seeds, red small round chilies, garlic crushed, curry leaves, green chilies and ginger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channa sukka (dry black grams)</title>
      <link>/post/channa-sukka-dry-black-grams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/channa-sukka-dry-black-grams/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Channa sukka (dry black grams)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vorn</title>
      <link>/post/vorn-sweet-lentils/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/vorn-sweet-lentils/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1 1&amp;frasl;2 cup, mung dal (yellow lentils, split) 2 cups, coconut milk 7 cups, water 1 cup, palm jaggery (cane-sugar), dark brown, grated 1 cup, palm jaggery, light brown 1 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp, cardamom powder 2 tbsp, rice flour 1 tsp, almonds, pistachio and cashew nuts, flakes 1 tbsp, almonds, pistachio and cashew nuts, coarsely ground 1 tbsp, raisins 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp, salt (optional)  Method: Soak mung dal in three cups water for an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French beans tel piyao</title>
      <link>/post/french-beans-tel-piyao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/french-beans-tel-piyao/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;French beans tel piyao&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprouted mung (green lentils)</title>
      <link>/post/sprouted-moong-green-lentils/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sprouted-moong-green-lentils/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;4 kg, mung (green whole lentils), soaked overnight 2 onions,medium-sized, sliced 2 tomatoes, medium-sized, sliced 3 green chilies, slit in half 1&amp;rdquo; ginger, chopped fine 6-7 garlic cloves, crushed 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp shahjeera (caraway seeds) 1 tsp, mustard seeds 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 1 tsp red chilly powder 1 tsp garam masala 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves, minced 10 curry leaves 4 tbsp, oil salt, as per taste 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water  Method: Soak the mung dal overnight and drain the water out the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhenda (Okra)</title>
      <link>/post/bhenda-okra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bhenda-okra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bhenda (Okra)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish cutlets</title>
      <link>/post/fish-cutlets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fish-cutlets/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  500 g fish of your choice (mackerel/tuna/kingfish) 1 potato, boiled and mashed 2 medium-sized onlion, chopped fine 3 green chillies ,chopped fine 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves, chopped fine 5-6 mint leaves, chopped fine 1 tbsp., ginger and garlic paste 1 tsp, turmeric powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. red chilly powder 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp, garam masala powder 2 tsp vinegar / Lemon juice salt, as per taste 2 cups, bread crumbs 2 cups, water 1 egg, beaten cooking oil (for frying)  Method: Clean the fish, cut into big pieces and put in a pan with 2 cups of water, 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mince with potatoes</title>
      <link>/post/mince-with-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mince-with-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  500g, minced meat (chicken, mutton, beef or pork) 2 onions, medium-sized, chopped fine 2 tomatoes, medium-sized, chopped 1 potato, large0sized, cut in cubes 1 tbsp. ginger and garlic paste 1 tsp, bafat powder 1&amp;frasl;2 inch, ginger, chopped fine 7 cloves, garlic, chopped fine 3 green chillies, slit in half 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. turmeric powder 1 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp black pepper powder 2 tbsp., lemon juice 1&amp;frasl;2 cup, coriander leaves, chopped fine 5-6 mint leaves, chopped fine salt as per taste soup cube (optional)  Whole spice:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semolina (Rava) Kheer</title>
      <link>/post/semolina-kheer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/semolina-kheer/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients :  1 cup semolina (rava) 3 tbsp sugar 2 tbsp, ghee (clarified butter) 1 1&amp;frasl;2 ltd, full cream / whole milk 200g condensed milk 150g fresh cream 1&amp;frasl;2 cup dry fruits (almonds, pistachios, cashew nuts), crushed coarsely 2 tbsp raisins (for garnishing) 1 tsp vanilla (food flavour) 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Kewra water (food flavour)  Method: Add ghee to a pan and fry semolina on low heat, stirring constantly to avoid burning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gajar ka Halwa</title>
      <link>/post/gajar-halwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gajar-halwa/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  5 cups, grated carrots 2 1&amp;frasl;2 cups, sugar 3 tbsp, milk powder 1 tsp, cardamom powder 1 1&amp;frasl;2 tbsp, butter almond/pistachio flakes (for garnishing)  Method In a pressure cooker, add the grated carrots, sugar and milk powder. Mix well till a wet sugar syrup is seen. Now close the pressure cooker and place the whistle, cooking on medium heat. Allow the whistle to go off twice and then switch the heat off, letting the cooker cool down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger and green peas pulao</title>
      <link>/post/burger-and-green-peas-pulao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/burger-and-green-peas-pulao/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Burger and green peas pulao&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Chilly Fry</title>
      <link>/post/burger-chilly-fry-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/burger-chilly-fry-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Burger Chilly Fry&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuvallo (ash pumpkin) bafat</title>
      <link>/post/kuvallo-ash-pumpkin-bafat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kuvallo-ash-pumpkin-bafat/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg Kuvallo (ash pumpkin), skinned, thin slices 1 cup coconut juice, thick 3 cups coconut juice, thin/diluted 3 onions, medium, sliced 2 tsp. ginger, chopped 5 cloves garlic, chopped 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp. turmeric powder 2 tsp. coriander powder 1 tsp. cumin powder 2 tsp. black pepper powder 1 tsp. garam masala powder 1 tbsp vinegar salt, to taste  For seasoning  10-12 green curry leaves 1 tsp.mustard seeds 2-3 small dried red chillies 3 tbsp oil  Method: Boil thin slices of the kuvallo (ash pumpkin) in water with turmeric and salt until when you see the pumpkin slices turn translucent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prawn chilly fry</title>
      <link>/post/prawn-chilly-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/prawn-chilly-fry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg. prawns, medium -sized, shelled and deveined 3 onions, medium, sliced 2 tomatoes, medium, sliced 4 green chillies, slit in half 1 tsp. ginger, chopped 2 tsp. garlic, chopped 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. red kashmir chilli powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. coriander powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. cumin powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp garam masala powder 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp turmeric powder 2 tbsp. lemon juice salt, to taste 3 tbsp, coriander leaves, chopped 15 green curry leaves 4 tbsp oil  Method: Marinate prawns with red chilly and turmeric powder and 1 tablespoon of lemon juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Pudding</title>
      <link>/post/bread-pudding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bread-pudding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bread Pudding&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ambot teek (fish curry)</title>
      <link>/post/ambot-teek-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ambot-teek-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ambot teek (fish curry)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sukka (Dry)</title>
      <link>/post/chicken-sukka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chicken-sukka/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chicken Sukka (Dry)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kheer</title>
      <link>/post/kheer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kheer/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients :  1 packet vermicelli (shev); broken into small pieces 2 liters milk, full cream 2 cups sugar 1 large can condensed milk 50g almond (badaam) flakes 50 g pistachio (pista) flakes 150g cashew nuts (kaju); coarse pieces 9-10 cardamom (elaichi) pieces; shelled and ground 2 pinches nutmeg (zaifal)  Method: Fry the pieces of vermicelli until golden brown and keep aside. Boil the milk with sugar and keep boiling till it is reduced to half its volume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginger Garlic Fish</title>
      <link>/post/ginger-garlic-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ginger-garlic-fish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yet another quick dish&amp;hellip;these are especially for those times when
guests come in uninvited or you’ve had enough of the chicken or meat.
Boneless fish is the best pick for this one&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinach (Palak) rice</title>
      <link>/post/palak-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/palak-rice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A variety of rice dish with finely cut spinach. If you’ve got some left
over rice, this dish really comes to the rescue !&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Chicken</title>
      <link>/post/chinese-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chinese-chicken/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chinese Chicken&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kale Desi Style</title>
      <link>/post/kale-desi-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kale-desi-style/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kale Desi Style&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken with Sesame seeds</title>
      <link>/post/chicken-with-sesame-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chicken-with-sesame-seeds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chicken with Sesame seeds&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mince pie</title>
      <link>/post/mincepie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mincepie/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg, chicken / mutton mince 2 onions, medium, finely chopped 3 potatoes, large, boiled and mashed 1&amp;frasl;2 tomato paste/puree 1 tbsp. yoghurt 1 tsp. ginger and garlic, chopped 3 green chillies, finely chopped 1 bunch, coriander leaves, chopped 12 mint leaves, chopped 1 tsp. garam masala powder 2 tsp. red chilli powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. turmeric powder 1 tsp. pepper, ground 1 tbsp. lemon juice salt, as per taste 1 tbsp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Roast</title>
      <link>/post/beef-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/beef-roast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Traditional Beef Roast&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Manchurian</title>
      <link>/post/chicken-manchurian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chicken-manchurian/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1.3 kg, chicken, cut into medium pieces, washed and drained 2&amp;rdquo; ginger, thick small cubes 9 garlic cloves, thick round pieces 7 green chillies, thick round pieces 1 tsp, ginger and garlic paste 2 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp chilly garlic sauce 2 tbsp corn flour 2 eggs 1 tsp bafat powder 1 soup cube 1&amp;frasl;2 cup oil  Method: Marinade the chicken pieces with ginger garlic paste, soy sauce, chilly garlic sauce, corn flour, eggs and bafat powder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maiche kaleez kodi (liver curry)</title>
      <link>/post/maiche-kaleez-kodi-liver-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/maiche-kaleez-kodi-liver-curry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Maiche kaleez kodi (liver curry)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton sukka Dry</title>
      <link>/post/mutton-suka-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mutton-suka-dry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1. For the boil:  2 kg mutton, cut into cubes 1 onion, small, sliced fine 1 tomato, small, sliced fine 1 green chilly, slit in between 1/4” ginger piece, chopped fine 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 3 garlic cloves 3 cloves 1 cardamom 2 cinnamon sticks, small 6 black pepper corns 1 bay leaf 1 soup cube or salt to taste  2. For the kadhai (cooking pot):  2 onions, medium-sized, sliced 2 tomatoes, medium-sized, sliced 2 green chilies, slit in half 5-6 garlic cloves, crushed 1&amp;frasl;2 cup fresh coconut, grated 2 tsp tamarind pulp 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves, chopped 6-7 curry leaves 2 tbsp oil 2 cloves (WS) 2 cinnamon sticks, small (WS) 5-6 black pepper corns (WS) 2 tsp red chilly powder (M) 2 tsp coriander powder (M) 1 tsp cumin powder (M) 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp turmeric powder (M) 1 tsp garam masala powder (M)  Method First boil the mutton with all the ingredients &amp;ldquo;for the boil&amp;rdquo; and keep aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bacon and eggs... with a twist!</title>
      <link>/post/bacon-and-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bacon-and-eggs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bacon and eggs&amp;hellip; with a twist!&amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggplant (brinjal) bartha</title>
      <link>/post/brinjal-bartha-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/brinjal-bartha-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eggplant (brinjal) bartha&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Creamy Chicken</title>
      <link>/post/baked-creamy-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/baked-creamy-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1 kg boneless chicken breast or thighs Vegetables of your choice (carrots, peas, potatoes, beans, broccoli etc.) 2 onions - small, finely chopped 1 cup fresh cream 1 cup grated cheese 4 tbsp all-purpose flour (maida) 2 cups milk 1&amp;frasl;2 cup melted butter 2 tbsp olive oil 1 tsp crushed black pepper 1 tsp salt  Method: Start with blanching the vegetables you wish to use in this dish and keep aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kori roti (Chicken curry)</title>
      <link>/post/kori-roti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kori-roti/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1 kg chicken (cut into medium sized pieces) 2 big onions (cut into fine slices) 2 green chillies 9 garlic cloves (crushed) 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger 1 can coconut cream 1 tbsp yogurt 1 tomato medium-sized 1 chicken soup cube 1 mug water  Powders:  3 tsp red chilly powder 2 tsp coriander (dhanya) powder 1 tsp cumin (jeera) powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric (haldi) powder  Whole spices:  9 black pepper corns 5 cloves 2-3 cinnamon sticks a pinch of fennel seeds 1 small cardamom *1&amp;frasl;2 tsp mustard seeds  Method: Cut the chicken into medium-sized pieces and bring to a boil (on a medium flame) with the water and chicken soup cube along with some whole spices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maiche maasli kodi (Mum&#39;s fish Curry)</title>
      <link>/post/masali-kodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/masali-kodi/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: (Serves 4-5 persons)  1 kg fish of your choice  For the paste:  2 onions, medium-size 2 tsps red chilly Powder 2 tsp coriander powder 1 tsp cumin powder 1 green chilly 7 garlic cloves 1 tomato - large / 1 tbsp curd 7 Vonti Solan (dried Monkey Jack seeds) / Tamarind (size of a lemon) 7-8 curry leaves 1&amp;frasl;2 freshly grated coconut / 1 can coconut milk Salt to taste  For the pan:  1 onion - small-sized; finely sliced 2 green chillies - slit in half 1&amp;frasl;2 inch ginger - finely chopped 2 tbsp oil 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves - finely chopped to garnish  Method: Grind all above ingredients to a fine paste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allu Dento (Colocasia) curry</title>
      <link>/post/allu-dento-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/allu-dento-curry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Allu Dento (Colocasia) curry&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crab masala</title>
      <link>/post/crab-masala/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/crab-masala/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1 kg, crabs 1&amp;frasl;4 cup coriander leaves, chopped fine  Roast and grind
 2 onions, large, finely sliced 2 tomatoes, medium, finely sliced 2 tsp coriander powder 1 tsp cumin powder 1 tsp black mustard seeds 6-7 garlic cloves 1 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger, minced 3 green chilies 1 tsp black pepper corns 3 cloves 2 cinnamon sticks, small 1 pinch ova 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp fennel seeds 8 red chillies (long and short) 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 1&amp;frasl;2 fresh coconut, grated 2 tbsp oil salt, as per taste  Method: Clean and cut the crabs into two halves and keep aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed chicken</title>
      <link>/post/stuffed-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/stuffed-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1.5 kg, chicken Whole spices (1 tsp coriander seeds, 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp cumin seeds, 7 black pepper corns, 1 tsp black mustard seeds, 3 cardamom, 7-8 cloves, 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp fennel seeds, 4 red chilli peppers, 3 bay leaves) 3 eggs, boiled, cut in halves 1 tbsp cooking oil  Marinade
 2 tsp ginger &amp;amp; garlic paste 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 2 tsp red Kashmir chilly powder 3&amp;frasl;4 tsp garam masala 1 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp salt  Stuffing</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>