<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mains on Maiche Jewan</title>
    <link>/categories/mains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mains on Maiche Jewan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/mains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger and green peas pulao</title>
      <link>/post/burger-and-green-peas-pulao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/burger-and-green-peas-pulao/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Burger and green peas pulao&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuvallo (ash pumpkin) bafat</title>
      <link>/post/kuvallo-ash-pumpkin-bafat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kuvallo-ash-pumpkin-bafat/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg Kuvallo (ash pumpkin), skinned, thin slices 1 cup coconut juice, thick 3 cups coconut juice, thin/diluted 3 onions, medium, sliced 2 tsp. ginger, chopped 5 cloves garlic, chopped 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp. turmeric powder 2 tsp. coriander powder 1 tsp. cumin powder 2 tsp. black pepper powder 1 tsp. garam masala powder 1 tbsp vinegar salt, to taste  For seasoning  10-12 green curry leaves 1 tsp.mustard seeds 2-3 small dried red chillies 3 tbsp oil  Method: Boil thin slices of the kuvallo (ash pumpkin) in water with turmeric and salt until when you see the pumpkin slices turn translucent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinach (Palak) rice</title>
      <link>/post/palak-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/palak-rice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A variety of rice dish with finely cut spinach. If you’ve got some left
over rice, this dish really comes to the rescue !&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mince pie</title>
      <link>/post/mincepie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mincepie/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1&amp;frasl;2 kg, chicken / mutton mince 2 onions, medium, finely chopped 3 potatoes, large, boiled and mashed 1&amp;frasl;2 tomato paste/puree 1 tbsp. yoghurt 1 tsp. ginger and garlic, chopped 3 green chillies, finely chopped 1 bunch, coriander leaves, chopped 12 mint leaves, chopped 1 tsp. garam masala powder 2 tsp. red chilli powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp. turmeric powder 1 tsp. pepper, ground 1 tbsp. lemon juice salt, as per taste 1 tbsp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Manchurian</title>
      <link>/post/chicken-manchurian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chicken-manchurian/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1.3 kg, chicken, cut into medium pieces, washed and drained 2&amp;rdquo; ginger, thick small cubes 9 garlic cloves, thick round pieces 7 green chillies, thick round pieces 1 tsp, ginger and garlic paste 2 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp chilly garlic sauce 2 tbsp corn flour 2 eggs 1 tsp bafat powder 1 soup cube 1&amp;frasl;2 cup oil  Method: Marinade the chicken pieces with ginger garlic paste, soy sauce, chilly garlic sauce, corn flour, eggs and bafat powder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maiche kaleez kodi (liver curry)</title>
      <link>/post/maiche-kaleez-kodi-liver-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/maiche-kaleez-kodi-liver-curry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Maiche kaleez kodi (liver curry)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kori roti (Chicken curry)</title>
      <link>/post/kori-roti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kori-roti/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1 kg chicken (cut into medium sized pieces) 2 big onions (cut into fine slices) 2 green chillies 9 garlic cloves (crushed) 1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo; ginger 1 can coconut cream 1 tbsp yogurt 1 tomato medium-sized 1 chicken soup cube 1 mug water  Powders:  3 tsp red chilly powder 2 tsp coriander (dhanya) powder 1 tsp cumin (jeera) powder 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric (haldi) powder  Whole spices:  9 black pepper corns 5 cloves 2-3 cinnamon sticks a pinch of fennel seeds 1 small cardamom *1&amp;frasl;2 tsp mustard seeds  Method: Cut the chicken into medium-sized pieces and bring to a boil (on a medium flame) with the water and chicken soup cube along with some whole spices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maiche maasli kodi (Mum&#39;s fish Curry)</title>
      <link>/post/masali-kodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/masali-kodi/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: (Serves 4-5 persons)  1 kg fish of your choice  For the paste:  2 onions, medium-size 2 tsps red chilly Powder 2 tsp coriander powder 1 tsp cumin powder 1 green chilly 7 garlic cloves 1 tomato - large / 1 tbsp curd 7 Vonti Solan (dried Monkey Jack seeds) / Tamarind (size of a lemon) 7-8 curry leaves 1&amp;frasl;2 freshly grated coconut / 1 can coconut milk Salt to taste  For the pan:  1 onion - small-sized; finely sliced 2 green chillies - slit in half 1&amp;frasl;2 inch ginger - finely chopped 2 tbsp oil 1&amp;frasl;2 cup coriander leaves - finely chopped to garnish  Method: Grind all above ingredients to a fine paste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed chicken</title>
      <link>/post/stuffed-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/stuffed-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1.5 kg, chicken Whole spices (1 tsp coriander seeds, 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp cumin seeds, 7 black pepper corns, 1 tsp black mustard seeds, 3 cardamom, 7-8 cloves, 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp fennel seeds, 4 red chilli peppers, 3 bay leaves) 3 eggs, boiled, cut in halves 1 tbsp cooking oil  Marinade
 2 tsp ginger &amp;amp; garlic paste 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp turmeric powder 2 tsp red Kashmir chilly powder 3&amp;frasl;4 tsp garam masala 1 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp salt  Stuffing</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>