<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dessert on Maiche Jewan</title>
    <link>/categories/dessert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dessert on Maiche Jewan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/dessert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vorn</title>
      <link>/post/vorn-sweet-lentils/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/vorn-sweet-lentils/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1 1&amp;frasl;2 cup, mung dal (yellow lentils, split) 2 cups, coconut milk 7 cups, water 1 cup, palm jaggery (cane-sugar), dark brown, grated 1 cup, palm jaggery, light brown 1 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp, cardamom powder 2 tbsp, rice flour 1 tsp, almonds, pistachio and cashew nuts, flakes 1 tbsp, almonds, pistachio and cashew nuts, coarsely ground 1 tbsp, raisins 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp, salt (optional)  Method: Soak mung dal in three cups water for an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gajar ka Halwa</title>
      <link>/post/gajar-halwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gajar-halwa/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  5 cups, grated carrots 2 1&amp;frasl;2 cups, sugar 3 tbsp, milk powder 1 tsp, cardamom powder 1 1&amp;frasl;2 tbsp, butter almond/pistachio flakes (for garnishing)  Method In a pressure cooker, add the grated carrots, sugar and milk powder. Mix well till a wet sugar syrup is seen. Now close the pressure cooker and place the whistle, cooking on medium heat. Allow the whistle to go off twice and then switch the heat off, letting the cooker cool down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semolina (Rava) Kheer</title>
      <link>/post/semolina-kheer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/semolina-kheer/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients :  1 cup semolina (rava) 3 tbsp sugar 2 tbsp, ghee (clarified butter) 1 1&amp;frasl;2 ltd, full cream / whole milk 200g condensed milk 150g fresh cream 1&amp;frasl;2 cup dry fruits (almonds, pistachios, cashew nuts), crushed coarsely 2 tbsp raisins (for garnishing) 1 tsp vanilla (food flavour) 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Kewra water (food flavour)  Method: Add ghee to a pan and fry semolina on low heat, stirring constantly to avoid burning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Pudding</title>
      <link>/post/bread-pudding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bread-pudding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bread Pudding&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kheer</title>
      <link>/post/kheer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kheer/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients :  1 packet vermicelli (shev); broken into small pieces 2 liters milk, full cream 2 cups sugar 1 large can condensed milk 50g almond (badaam) flakes 50 g pistachio (pista) flakes 150g cashew nuts (kaju); coarse pieces 9-10 cardamom (elaichi) pieces; shelled and ground 2 pinches nutmeg (zaifal)  Method: Fry the pieces of vermicelli until golden brown and keep aside. Boil the milk with sugar and keep boiling till it is reduced to half its volume.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>